听力考试正式开始。 Listen to the next question.
When does the Shopney Your School open?
It opens at 8 a.m. from Monday to Friday, but at weekends it opens at 8.30 a.m. When does the Shopney Your School open?
It opens at 8 a.m. from Monday to Friday, but at weekends it opens at 8.30 a.m. Listen to the next question.
The little cat made a sound like a whisper last night.
What happened to it?
I think it felt a little sick.
The little cat made a sound like a whisper last night.
What happened to it?
I think it felt a little sick.
Listen to the next question.
How much are the things?
The blue tie is 25 yuan and the black socks are 30 yuan.
Listen to the next question.
Sarah, do you like playing basketball?
No, it's difficult for me, but my brother likes playing it and he is good at it.
Listen to the next question.
Here is a nice photo.
Is the boy with black hair your brother, Jane?
No, he isn't.
My brother has brown hair and he doesn't wear glasses.
Here is a nice photo.
Is the boy with black hair your brother, Jane?
No, he isn't.
My brother has brown hair and he doesn't wear glasses.
Listen to the next question.
Good evening.
May I take your order?
Yes.
What kind of noodles do you have?
We have beef noodles, mutton noodles and chicken noodles.
Are there any vegetables in the beef noodles?
Yes.
There are some potatoes.
Okay.
I'd like beef noodles.
Sure.
What size would you like?
Large, please.
And do you have any drinks? Of course.
We have tea, milk and orange juice.
Orange juice, please.
Okay.
One large bowl of beef noodles and an orange juice.
How much are they?
A large bowl of beef noodles is ten dollars and the orange juice is four dollars.
Okay.
Thanks a lot. You're welcome.
Good evening.
May I take your order?
I take your order.
Yes.
What kind of noodles do you have?
We have beef noodles, mutton noodles and chicken noodles.
Are there any vegetables in the beef noodles?
Yes.
There are some potatoes.
Okay.
I'd like beef noodles.
Sure.
What size would you like?
Large, please.
And do you have any drinks? Of course.
We have tea, milk and orange juice.
Orange juice, please.
Okay.
One large bowl of beef noodles and an orange juice.
How much are they?
A large bowl of beef noodles is ten dollars and the orange juice is four dollars.
Okay.
Thanks a lot. You're welcome.
Listen to the next question.
Hi, I am Jack.
I like animals very much.
I often go to the zoo to see animals on Sundays.
My brother Mike also likes animals.
So he goes there with me.
There are many animals in the zoo, such as tigers, elephants, giraffes, bears and many other animals.
Tigers are very dangerous.
They usually live alone and catch many kinds of animals for food.
So I don't like them.
My brother likes elephants because elephants are tall and strong.
They can play soccer and draw.
They can also help people do many things.
Many people like giraffes because giraffes are beautiful and interesting.
Zebras are my favorite animals.
They are very cute.
They are from Africa.
They are black and white.
Hi, I am Jack.
I like animals very much.
I often go to the zoo to see animals on Sundays.
My brother Mike also likes animals.
So he goes there with me.
There are many animals in the zoo, such as tigers, elephants, giraffes, bears and many other animals.
Tigers are very dangerous.
They usually live alone and catch many kinds of animals for food.
So I don't like them.
My brother likes elephants because elephants are tall and strong.
They can play soccer and draw.
They can also help people do many things.
Many people like giraffes because giraffes are beautiful and interesting.
Zebras are my favorite animals.
They are very cute.
They are from Africa.
They are black and white.
They are very cute.
They are very cute. Thank you.